<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Grain Vision</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="login_password_hint2">Repeat Password</string>
    <string name="reg_passwordS_hint">Retype Password</string>
    <string name="alamat_hint">Alamat</string>
    <string name="login_phone_hint">phone number format : +62811220202 </string>

    <string name="upload">Grain Vision 2021 v1 adalah aplikasi kecerdasan buatan pendeteksi jenis gandum. \n untuk penggunaannya Upload foto dengan mengklik icon photo, aplikasi akan secara otomatis mendeteksi jenis gandum sesuai dengan foto yang di upload "</string>
    <string name="uploaded">  Setelah foto selesai di upload, maka aplikasi akan secara otomatis mengenerate angka statistik "</string>
    <string name="hasil"> Secara otomatis hasil dari tampilan akan tersimpan di history</string>
    <string name="chart"> Secara otomatis akan menampilkan chart</string>
    <string name="details">Details"</string>
    <string name="reg_password_hint">password</string>
    <string name="beras_contoh">Berikut Contoh posisi beras yang benar untuk meningkatkan akurasi"</string>
    <string name="beras_contohb">Contoh posisi beras yang benar \n untuk mendapatkan hasil dan akurasi yang maksimal"</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">Lets Start</string>
    <string name="en_slide1">The Grain Vision is an artificial intelligence application that can analyze the quality and variety of grains. \nThis application is very easy to use, users only need to take a photo of grain by click photo icon and then upload the photo  or select from photo gallery. This application will automatically generate reports grain types and varieties </string>
    <string name="en_slide2">To generate valid data and improve accuracy, the grains need to be placed on a dark background (black, dark blue, dark green or dark red)  and at distance from each other. \nNote : a white or bright background will make the data inaccurate and invalid</string>
    <string name="en_slide3">After the photo is uploaded, the application will automatically generate report of grain analysis </string>
    <string name="en_slide4">And will generate report chart </string>
    <string name="en_slide5">  The results will be stored in history and to view historical data,  user only needs to click on date to be displayed</string>
    <string name="en_slide6"> VERSIONS :</string>
</resources>
